(Mrs Cooper:)Shelly does not like change.
(Sheldon:)Oh, true.
(Sheldon:)But all the clenching
in the world will not keep
(Sheldon:)testicles in your abdomen.
(Penny:)Hey, sorry,
got caught up at work.
Hi, Beverly!
(Dr Hofstadter:)Hello.
(giggles)
(Dr Hofstadter:)Oh, okay.
(chuckles)
(Penny:)Sorry, I forgot.
(Sheldon:)You remember my mother.
Oh, yes. Hi, Mary!
(Sheldon:)Good to see you
again, dear.
(Penny:)Ah, yeah, now that's
what I'm talking about.
(Leonard:)So, Mom, you haven't seen Penny
since we got engaged.
(Penny:)Oh, yeah, let me
show you the ring.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Oh, lovely.
(Dr Hofstadter:)Must have been
very expensive.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, not at all.
(Sheldon:)No, we, uh, found
a place online
(Sheldon:)that, uh, repurposes
diamond drill bits.
(Leonard:)We did not. That's not true.
(Leonard:)Can I speak to you alone
for a second?
(Sheldon:)Oh, sure.
(Leonard:)It came from Tiffany's.
(chuckles)
(Sheldon:)You mean the box, right?
Keep walking!
(Penny:)Really doesn't matter to me
how much he spent on the ring.